North Pacific Program, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Records UA189
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
North Pacific Program, Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy Records
1981 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
North Pacific Program
Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy
UA189
12.95 Linear Feet
10 Digital Object(s)
280 Kilobytes
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Arrangement
The collection is organized into four series: Subject files; Audiovisual materials; John Perry records; and Unprocessed accessions.
Biographical / Historical
The North Pacific Program (1985-1995) was part of the Fletcher School of Law and Diplomacy. Directed by John Curtis Perry, the program endeavored to examine the political, economic, intellectual, and cultural trends of the countries that fall on the Pacific Rim. The countries represented in the program were the United States, Canada, Mexico, the former Soviet Union, China, Japan, North Korea, and South Korea. The program was not a formal field of study; rather it focused on enhancing the Fletcher curriculum with classes on culture and economics from the area of the North Pacific.
Scope and Contents
This collection documents the North Pacific Program directed by John Curtis Perry at Tufts University. Materials include correspondence, newspaper articles, student papers, funding research, photographs and video tapes from 1985 to 1995. The primary focus of the collection is the planning associated with running the annual North Pacific Program seminar. This collection also contains seminar schedules and trip itineraries, reports, budgets, and audiocassette tapes of lectures at the Fletcher School's North Pacific Program (NPP), and information about guest lecturers from the Sanwa Lecture Series, which was run by the NPP.
Foreign affairs; Curriculum and Instruction; Foreign affairs; Curriculum and Instruction -- Course Material
- Subject Files, 1981 -- 1996; 1985 -- 1999; UA189.001; 7.2 Linear Feet; 10 Digital Object(s); 280 Kilobytes
  Scope and Contents
  This series includes correspondence, newspaper articles, student papers, and funding research for the North Pacific Program from 1985 to 1995. The bulk of the material is correspondence concerning the organization of the annual field seminar.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Allison-Sov. Far E. update, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - [Alumni] Mailing lists, 1991; UA189.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - [APEC participants], 1994; UA189.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - [APEC report] APEC report, 1994; UA189.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    1 of 5.
  - [APEC report Apec applications], 1994; UA189.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    2 of 5.
  - [APEC report] Correspondence/attendees, 1994; UA189.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    3 of 5.
  - [APEC report] Correspondence-speakers, 1994; UA189.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    4 of 5.
  - [APEC report] Correspondence, 1994; UA189.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    5 of 5.
  - Applications completed for internships and language study grants, 1986 -- 1987; UA189.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - [BCOM] BCOM bills, 1991; UA189.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - [Budget Printing services], 1992; UA189.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    1 of 3.
  - [Budget] Budget breakdown, 1992; UA189.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    2 of 3.
  - [Budget] Summer funds avail 1/22/92, 1992; UA189.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    3 of 3.
  - Business persons - Sakhalia, 1992; UA189.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    1 of 2.
  - Business persons - Sakhalia, 1992; UA189.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    2 of 2.
  - [Canada] Dunsmuir lodge Univ. Victoria, 1992; UA189.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - [Canada] Canada/CCACD, 1989 -- 1991; UA189.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - CGP, 1992; UA189.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - CGP application, 1992; UA189.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - [China Institute of Current World Affairs], 1991; UA189.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - [China] China seminar? notes, 1990; UA189.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - [China] China O Dougherty, 1992 -- 1993; UA189.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence] So-IL correspondence, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    1 of 4.
  - [Correspondence] Seoul-forum correspondence, 1994; UA189.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    2 of 4.
  - [Correspondence] APEC correspondence, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    3 of 4.
  - [Correspondence] Correspondence Mr. Ju, 1994; UA189.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    4 of 4.
  - [Correspondence] 1990 correspondence in, UA189.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence] Recent letters out, 1996; UA189.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence 1993-1994] Correspondence out, UA189.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence 1993-94] IBP '93-94 corr. in, 1993 -- 1994; UA189.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence 1993-94] Correspondence out, 1994; UA189.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1993; UA189.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1993; UA189.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1993; UA189.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1994; UA189.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1994; UA189.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1994; UA189.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence 94-95] Faxes JCP, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - [Correspondence 94-95] '95-'95 corresp., 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence [general], 1995; UA189.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - [Development office], 1993 -- 1994; UA189.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Development prospects, 1993; UA189.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
  - Environment, 1991; UA189.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Excursions, 1990; UA189.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] NP instititute info, 1990; UA189.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    1 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] CV's, 1989; UA189.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    2 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] F-H 1987 LTB memos to students, UA189.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    3 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] F-H Fletcher Alumnae/i letter, 1987; UA189.001.002.00006 (Box 1)
    4 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] NP relevant readings, 1988; UA189.001.002.00007 (Box 1)
    5 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] Info from students interested in 1988 Hokkaido seminar or internships, UA189.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    6 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido] F-H application form, 1988; UA189.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    7 of 7.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido brochure drafts], 1985; UA189.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    1 of 2. Note on folder says ' 2nd set revisions'.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido], 1985 -- 1986; UA189.001.002.00011 (Box 1)
    2 of 2. Note on folder says '86 book=printers $ info'.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87] Fletcher-Hokkaido '86 forum, 1986 -- 1987; UA189.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    1 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87] NPP brochure, 1987; UA189.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    2 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87] Book orders, 1987; UA189.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    3 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87 Grades], 1986; UA189.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    4 of 6. Note on folder says 'undergraduate papers diplomacy 208'.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87] D235, 1986; UA189.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    5 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido '86-'87] DIP 257 philanthopy, 1987; UA189.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    6 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987] JCP workshop Hokkaido 1987 bibliographies, UA189.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987] F-H 1987 students, UA189.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987] Faculty topics and readings, UA189.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987] Fletcher Hokkaido 1987], UA189.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987], UA189.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido Program '88], 1988; UA189.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] Fletcher/Harvard Hokkaido '88 student, UA189.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] F-H daily schedules, UA189.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] Facebook F-H, UA189.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    3 of 6. Note on folder says check '88 spellings against this facebook.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] Handouts of lectures F-H, UA189.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    4 of 6.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] Hokkaido forum brochure Hokkaido magazine, UA189.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1988] Workshop and lecture notes from F-H, UA189.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido Seminar (1988)] Fletcher/Hokkaido applications, UA189.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    1 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988) Biography], UA189.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    2 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988) Resumes], UA189.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    3 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Outgoing correspondence, UA189.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
    4 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Miscellaneous, UA189.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
    5 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Incoming correspondence, UA189.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
    6 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Workshops, 1987; UA189.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    7 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Matsue project Hokkaido, 1986; UA189.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    8 of 9.
  - [Fletcher/Hokkaido seminar (1988)] Fletcher-Hokkaido program, 1985; UA189.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    9 of 9.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1989 Notes], UA189.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1989 Notes], UA189.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1989] Master copies-1989 info meeting handouts, UA189.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    1 of 3. Note on folder says 'Hokkaido application, agenda, schdule, seminar description'.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1989] 1989 Schedules, participants, faculty cvs, UA189.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 1989 Newspaper clippings], UA189.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher N. Pacific Institute] FNPI blueprint, 1989; UA189.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher N. Pacific Institute Correspondence], 1989 -- 1990; UA189.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido seminar brochure] All descriptive paragraphs, 1990; UA189.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido seminar brochure] Off draft, 1990; UA189.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher Hokkaido 5 year brochure] Pagination, 1990; UA189.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
    1 of 3. Notes about scheduling on folder.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 5 year brochure] 5yr. anniv. publication, 1990; UA189.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
    2 of 3. Notes about scheduling on folder.
  - [Fletcher-Hokkaido 5 year brochure Hokkaido Herald], 1988; UA189.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
  - Fletcher NP Program paper (by archetype), 1992; UA189.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
  - [Fletcher NPP] Seoul, 1991; UA189.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Leadersh/foundats, 1990; UA189.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] MacArthur, 1991; UA189.001.002.00054 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Pew Ch. Trust draft, 1991; UA189.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] RBP, 1992; UA189.001.002.00056 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Japan Foundation grant renewal, 1992; UA189.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Saehan, 1993; UA189.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Sasakawa, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Marshall Foundation, 1992; UA189.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Miti-Shozo Takada, 1992; UA189.001.002.00061 (Box 2)
  - [Funding] Sample proposal, letters, funds, 1989 -- 1991; UA189.001.002.00062 (Box 2)
  - [Funding proposals] H/Perry low CGP, 1992; UA189.001.002.00063 (Box 2)
    1 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Education, 1992; UA189.001.002.00064 (Box 2)
    2 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Tokyo Club, 1992; UA189.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
    3 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] JCP funds, 1992; UA189.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
    4 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Pan Denn memos/notes letters, 1991 -- 1992; UA189.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
    5 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Full proposal/budget, 1991; UA189.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
    6 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Generic proposal, 1991; UA189.001.002.00069 (Box 2)
    7 of 8.
  - [Funding proposals] Letter of inquiry, 1991; UA189.001.002.00070 (Box 2)
    8 of 8.
  - [Funding sources] Japanese foundations, 1991 -- 1993; UA189.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
  - [Funding 1992] Jap-funds, UA189.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - [Funding 1992] Proposal Japan, UA189.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - [Funding 1992] Foundation information, 1988 -- 1991; UA189.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - [Funding 1992], UA189.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
    4 of 5. Dnlb in residence proposals
  - [Funding 1992] Natl Bureau of Asian Res, UA189.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Gateway Japan, 1993; UA189.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - High school teachers-summer, 1994; UA189.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Criteria for Hokkaido seminarians (preliminary list-11/21/85), 1985; UA189.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Hokkaido press release, 1985; UA189.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Hokkaido student file, 1985; UA189.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido], 1985; UA189.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Correspondence, 1985; UA189.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Hokkaido week in Massachusetts, 1992; UA189.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Sister state-Ma-Hok, 1992; UA189.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] 1992 correspondence, UA189.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] NORPAC, 1991; UA189.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Hokkaido history, 1991; UA189.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido] Sapporo guest house, 1992; UA189.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986], UA189.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] Perry file-memos, UA189.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] Hokkaido 1986-participants, UA189.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] NPP students, 1986 -- 1987; UA189.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] NPP- advisory council, 1987; UA189.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] bibliographic information-Japan, 1985; UA189.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] Addresses, UA189.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] Japan internships BoT and Sanwa bank internship info recruit correspondence, UA189.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1984-1986] NPP-publications, UA189.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] Hokkaido, UA189.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] NPP brochure, UA189.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] Newspaper articles/OTA's papers, UA189.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] F-H report 1986 addendum, UA189.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] Hokkaido preparations, UA189.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] Essays by Ota, UA189.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986] Hokkaido - USSR participation DPRK PRC, UA189.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1987] Correspondence LTB, 1995; UA189.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1987] Fletcher-Hokkaido, 1985 -- 1986; UA189.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1987] Hokkaido 1987 - readings, UA189.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1987] F-H '87 students cv's and photos, UA189.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
    5 of 6. Note on folder says 'Fletcher-Hokkaido 1987 student participants, directory and course schedules'.
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1987] Japanese and homestay info, UA189.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] Brochure, UA189.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] F-H '86 stuff, UA189.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] Hokkaido 88 faculty cv's, 1988; UA189.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] Fletcher-Hokkaido readings-1988-, 1988 -- 1989; UA189.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] Kenichiro Hirano, UA189.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1986-1989] Fletcher Hokkaido program, UA189.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1987] Schedule Hokkaido 1987 favulty, UA189.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1987] Hokkaido favulty 1987 cv's, UA189.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Forum speakers-panelists '88 correspond. and info, UA189.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
    1 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Chiba fax and letters F-H '88 Japan fac, UA189.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
    2 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Memos sent to students and faculty F-H 88 (details...)(meetings etc...) 1st semester schedule, UA189.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
    3 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Memos to students on NP opportunities and Hokkaido seminar and meetings descriptions-announcements, 1986; UA189.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
    4 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Repeat memos and correspondence, 1984; UA189.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
    5 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] F-H '86-'88 wrap up meeting student-faculty recommendations suggestions, 1986 -- 1988; UA189.001.003.00054 (Box 3)
    6 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Letters to Soviet, CHinese and Harvard students, UA189.001.003.00055 (Box 3)
    7 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] FYI's from JCP, UA189.001.003.00056 (Box 3)
    8 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Fletcher country stats., UA189.001.003.00057 (Box 3)
    9 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Application, UA189.001.003.00058 (Box 3)
    10 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Hokkaido acceptances, UA189.001.003.00059 (Box 3)
    11 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] NP student lists, 1987 -- 1989; UA189.001.003.00060 (Box 3)
    12 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] The Hoppoken Center info/Sapporo map Alpha Tomamu info, Sapporo Sun Plaza, UA189.001.003.00061 (Box 3)
    13 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Letters to faculty, administration F-H, 1987 -- 1988; UA189.001.003.00062 (Box 3)
    14 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Japan Society of Boston letterhead, UA189.001.003.00063 (Box 3)
    15 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Mass-Hokkaido committee 1988 endorsement letters Knapp, UA189.001.003.00064 (Box 3)
    16 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Infor packet for final meeting (including waiver forms), UA189.001.003.00065 (Box 3)
    17 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] F-H seminar '88 schedule and workshop assignment orientation materials, UA189.001.003.00066 (Box 3)
    18 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] 1989 Miti-Jetro (Ogawa), UA189.001.003.00067 (Box 3)
    19 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] Visa application and letters and addresses, UA189.001.003.00068 (Box 3)
    20 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989 George C. Marshall Foundation], UA189.001.003.00069 (Box 3)
    21 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1988-1989] 1985 schedule, UA189.001.003.00070 (Box 3)
    22 of 22.
  - [Hokkaido 1989] 1989 Hokkaido '89 particip. lists, UA189.001.003.00071 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1989] Itineraries '89 waivers, UA189.001.003.00072 (Box 3)
  - [Hokkaido 1989] Student 1989 Hokkaido workshop selections, UA189.001.003.00073 (Box 3)
  - Hokkaido, 1989; UA189.001.003.00074 (Box 3)
  - Hopkins Nanjing Center, 1988; UA189.001.003.00075 (Box 3)
  - [Information on students '93-'94] Misc. students, 1992; UA189.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Institute, 1990; UA189.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - [Interns] Interns, 1994; UA189.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - [Interns] '95 interns, 1995; UA189.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Jackson Foundation, 1992; UA189.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] US-Japan collaborative education articles, 1990; UA189.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] Earlham College Japan program, 1990; UA189.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] JCP-honor from Japan, 1991; UA189.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] Japan alums, 1991; UA189.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] CEAS newsletter, 1992; UA189.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - [Japan] Hirabayashi papers, 1992; UA189.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - [Japan Economic Foundation] Japan Economic Foundation, 1994 -- 1995; UA189.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - [Japan Economic Foundation] Asian Found., 1992; UA189.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - [Japan Economic Foundation] Ford Foundation, 1992; UA189.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - [Japan Economic Foundation] Hitachi, 1992; UA189.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - [Japan Economic Foundation] Japan Econ. Foundation, 1994; UA189.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - [Japan information] Japan brochures, 1988 -- 1994; UA189.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - [Japan information] Misc. info on Japan-grants, politic, 1990; UA189.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - [Kathleen Cooke Ryan application], 1992; UA189.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - [Korea] CKS newsletter, 1992; UA189.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - [Korea] DPRK, 1991; UA189.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - [Korea] North Korea news, 1992 -- 1994; UA189.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - [Korea] Korea file, 1991; UA189.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - [Korea] Spring 1992 lectures, UA189.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Korea Foundation, 1994; UA189.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Kor funds budget, 1992 -- 1993; UA189.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Leadership, 1992 -- 1993; UA189.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Unpublished mss, 1990; UA189.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Keio paper, The U.S., Japan and the new world (manuscript), 1990; UA189.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
    2 of 3. This date is aprroximate.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Manuscript drafts, 1990; UA189.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] North Korea: myths and realities (foreign policy) 5/89, 1989; UA189.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Please, Japan return the favor: occupy us (New York Times, 1981; UA189.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Manuscript (Prof. Perry) the crane and the pheonix, 1990; UA189.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] The new world of the North Pacific Japan ass. of inter. relations 8/29/86, 1986; UA189.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] The Soviet far east: American opp..(New York Times) and L.A. (1990), UA189.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Orient express the US, Japan and high speed....., 1989; UA189.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] The trans-mongolian express (article), 1990; UA189.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Asahi Shimbun article, 1991; UA189.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
    1 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Asahi Shimbun article/Nov. 2, 1993; UA189.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
    2 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Asahi op ed - Nov. 2, 1993 wanted:a North Pacific organization, UA189.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
    3 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] A visit to the hermit kingdom (JCP and DZ), 1993; UA189.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
    4 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Articles (Bun you associates) 9/87, 1987; UA189.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
    5 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Changing transportation technologies and their impact on Hokkaido (paper given in Sapporo), 1988; UA189.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Chicago Tribune articles, 1983; UA189.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
    7 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Look Japan articles 9due 3/17/82), 1982; UA189.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
    8 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] Manuscript - America, Japan, and the great northern crescent and the telectronic commonwealth-J.C. Perry, 1984; UA189.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
    9 of 10.
  - [Manuscripts and articles] New book, 1982; UA189.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
    10 of 10.
  - [Meeting notes] Misc. notes from meeting re: 90, 1990; UA189.001.004.00048 (Box 4)
  - [Meeting notes] 1989-1990 JCP random notes and meeting notes, UA189.001.004.00049 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico-correspondence] J.C.P. correspondence, 1995; UA189.001.004.00050 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico-correspondence] IBP correspondence, 1995; UA189.001.004.00051 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Chinese students to Mexico, 1995; UA189.001.004.00052 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Articles-Mexico, 1995; UA189.001.004.00053 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] NPP-, 1993; UA189.001.004.00054 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Mitsubishi, 1995; UA189.001.004.00055 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Mexico travel, 1995; UA189.001.004.00056 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Mexico - attendees, 1995; UA189.001.004.00057 (Box 4)
  - [Mexico '95] Correspondence manuel, 1994; UA189.001.004.00058 (Box 4)